Contact

ojiakugoodness@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/drogochukwu-ojiaku-26ab70130 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare
Hospitals
Healthcare Management

Certifications

Board Certified Family Nurse Practitioner

Dr. Ogochukwu Ojiaku

DNP, MSN, APRN, FNP-C, PMHNP-BC Doctoral Prepared, Dual Certified, Experienced Nurse Practitioner

Greater Atlanta Area

Summary

Personal Data: Ogochukwu Ojiaku DNP, MSN, FNP-C,

PMHNP-BC

ojiakugoodness@gmail.com, ogochifrank@yahoo.com

Education: DNP/ PMHNP-BC - Brandman University, FNP-C-

Chamberlain College of Nursing

A Nurse practitioner with dual Certification in Family Practice and Psychiatric Mental Health focused on providing quality, holistic care to patients of all ages, and maintaining direct lines of communication with the patients and the entire healthcare team. Possession of solid wealth of experience taking care of people with diverse healthcare issues, including mental illnesses. A Doctor of Nursing Practice Graduate, with Post Masters' Certification in Psychiatric Mental Health. Prior to obtaining her Doctoral Degree in Nursing, Ms. Ojiaku first obtained MSN/ Family Nurse Practitioner degree from Chamberlain College of Nursing Addison IL. Her passion for patient care, and experience will give potential employers the flexibility to place her in a broad range of demanding situations, with the confidence that she will undertake her duties professionally and effectively. With her extensive RN/ Nurse practitioner experience, Ms. Ojiaku is confident that she can make a substantial contribution to any company that employs her. Ms. OJiaku works well under pressure, she is reliable, and she carries out tasks in a thorough, precise manner. Below are some of her key strengths, qualifications and accomplishments.

- Excellent communication skills, both over the phone and face to face
- Ability to identify and implement strategies timely to meet objectives
- Possession of the drive and the determination to exceed set goals
- Extensive experience in inpatient, outpatient hospice, and palliative care services and Medsurg,

oncology, geriatrics/ extended care, and psychiatry.

- Diagnosis and management of common, complex and chronic conditions.
- Possession of Solid Medical- Surgical experience
- Experienced in effective collaboration with interdisciplinary team members.
- knowledgeable of admission criteria, assessment, treatment, referral etc.

Experience

Atlanta VA Medical Center
6 years 1 month

MSN, APRN, FNP-C

June 2014 - Present (6 years 1 month)

USA

DNP, MSN, APRN, FNP-C, PMHNP-BC- Seeking part time Telepsych. employment within and outside of GA June 2014 - Present (6 years 1 month)

Works in Veteran's Affairs Hospital in Decatur GA

A Nurse practitioner, focused on providing quality care, and maintaining direct lines of communication with the patients and the entire healthcare team.

Possession of outstanding leadership, and interpersonal skills. More than 12 years of experience in nursing and healthcare field. Seeking for a position in a facility, that diagnoses and treats patients with both common and complex health conditions.

Certifications

Certified family nurse practitioner in the state of Georgia

Possession of DEA #

Basic Cardiac Life Support (CPR) – American Heart Association- current

ASLS- Advanced stroke life support for hospital providers- current

ONS certified- Member Oncology Nursing society

Certified Medical Surgical Registered Nurse- current

Highlights

- Patient-centered care
- · Health and wellness expert

- Preventive care specialist
- Sound judgement
- Knowledgeable in interpretation of lab result, evaluation, and appropriate treatment
- Collaboration and appropriate referral

Veterans Affair Medical Center Registered Nurse

Education

Brandman University, Part of the Chapman University System Doctor of Nursing Practice, PMHNP-BC, FNP-C · (2014 - 2016)